Inventory of the Vertical (Subject) Files, 1831 - [ongoing]
Vertical (Subject) Files, 1831 - [ongoing]
- Faculty: Individuals
  - Stapleton, Bridget
  - Steady, Filomina Clarice
  - Stearns, Malcolm Jr.
  - Stedman, Murray S.
  - Steele, Robert
  - Steffenson, James L.
  - Steinberg, Susan J.
  - Stemler, Steven
  - Stephenson, Andrew
  - Stepto, Michele L.
  - Stepto, Robert Burns
  - Stern, Daniel
  - Stern, Frederick William
  - Sternheim, Marci Bess
  - Stevens, Amy Elizabeth
  - Stevenson, Brenda E.
  - Stevenson, Clay
  - Stevenson, James A.
  - Stewart, Abigail
  - Stewart, Cynthia
  - Stigler, Andrew L.
  - Stock, Jurgen
  - Stokes, Joseph Morgan
  - Storrs, William Lucius
  - Stowe, William M.
  - Straker, Brenda J. Skelley
  - Straker, Reverend Ian B.
  - Strand, Mark
  - Strand, Richard F.
  - Strauss, Melvin
  - Strickland, Charles S.
  - Striegel-Moore, Ruth H.
  - Strong, Frederick C. III
  - Strong, Robert L.
  - Stubblefield, John
  - Stubbs, Frederick Winsor
  - Sturges, Robert S.
  - Subrahmanyam, Ramesh
  - Suhr, Susan Edna
  - Sullivan, Garrett A.
  - Sullivan, Lisa Y.
  - Sultan, Sonia
  - Sumarsam
  - Sundaram, Sheila
  - Swaim, Elizabeth
  - Swanson, J. Elmer
  - Swanson, Wayne R.
  - Swartz, David
  - Sweeney, John Worth
  - Swift, David Everett
  - Swinehart, Kirk Davis
  - Swinney, Susan Virginia
  - Symmes, Anne Cleves
  - Szegedy-Maszak, Andrew
  - Szeliga, Irene
  - Szogyi, Alexander William
  - Tagliacozzo, Eric
  - Tamminen, Suzanna
  - Tammuz, Esther
  - Taraba, Suzy
  - Tarr, Judith
  - Tashiro, Tom
  - Tatge, Pamela
  - Tawil, Ezra F.
  - Taylor, Edwin F.
  - Taylor, Kenneth A.
  - Taylor, Robert
  - Tedlock, Dennis
  - Telfair, Tula
  - Tempel, Patricia C.
  - Tennenhouse, Leonard
  - Tenzer, Morton Jay
  - Testerman, Donna
  - Teter, Magdalena
  - Thiers, Valerie
  - Thobani, Mateen
  - Thomas, Ellen
  - Thompson, Becky
  - Thompson, David A. III
  - Thompson, David Duane
  - Thompson, Sarah
  - Thompson, W. R.
  - Thomson, Alexander
  - Thornton, Clifford
  - Thurman, Robert A. F.
  - Tierney, James
  - Timothy, Robin
  - Tipton, Frank Benjamin
  - Tischler, Max
  - Titus, David A.
  - Tobias, Sheila (2 folders)
  - Todd, H. David
  - Tokes, Rudolf Leslie
  - Tololyan, Khachig
  - Tondeur, Philippe
  - Tong, Enzheng
  - Tong, Hing
  - Topshe, Joyce
  - Torii, Namino
  - Torrey, Ray Ethan
  - Trask, David Frederic
  - Traube, Elizabeth
  - Trefny, John Ulric
  - Treatham, Edwina
  - Trest, Theodore Louis
  - Trousdale, William L.
  - True, Charles Kitterdge
  - Truscott, James George
  - Tsuge, Gen'ichi
  - Tubbs, Bill
  - Tucker, Jennifer
  - Turco, Alfred
  - Turgi, Mary Catherine
  - Turner, John
  - Turner, Robert S. Jr.
  - Turrentine, John William
  - Tyler, Sandra
  - Ugresic, Dubravka
  - Ulanov, Alexander
  - Ulrich, Henri
  - Underwood, Kenneth Wilson
  - Upgreen, Arthur Reinhold
  - Vaidhyanathan, Siva
  - Vakil, Cyrus M.
  - Van Benschoten, James Cooke
  - Van Dusen, Albert E.
  - Van Dyke, Karl Skillman
  - Van Rees, Edward H.
  - Van Saun, William
  - Van Tuyl, Jocelyn C.
  - Vance, David
  - Vanderhaar, Gerard A.
  - Vann, Richard Tilman
  - Varecamp, Johan
  - Vega, Estaban
  - Viggiani, Carl A.
  - Viglino, Giovanni
  - Villatoro, Gillman
  - Vincent, John
  - Vino, John A.
  - Vinson, Stacey A.
  - Visona, Paolo
  - Viswanathan, T.
  - Vogel, Robert C.
  - Vogt, Victor Ervin
  - Von Winbush, Samuel
  - Vonalt, Larry Paul
  - Vose, Clement Ellery (2 folders)
  - Voth, Greg
  - Wagers, Charles Herndon
  - Wagner, R. R.
  - Wagoner, Phillip
  - Wagoner, Rieko
  - Waiveris, Charles
  - Waldrop, Bernard
  - Waldrop, Rosemary and Keith
  - Walker, Clarence
  - Walker, Dorothy L.
  - Walker, Willard Brewer
  - Wallace, John S.
  - Wallace, Richard Jay
  - Wallace, Willard Mosher
  - Walsh, John W.
  - Walzer, Michael
  - Wang, Chung-Lan
  - Ward, William Roger
  - Ware, William Joseph
  - Wasilewska, Anita
  - Watts, Jerry
  - Watts, Linda S.
  - Weber, Robert James
  - Wedeen, Lisa
  - Weir, Michael
  - Weis, Edward Wayland
  - Weissberger, Edward
  - Weissman, Hope Phyllis
  - Weitzer, William
  - Wells, Marion A.
  - Weltman, John J.
  - Wendt, G. Richard
  - Wensinger, Arthur S. "Jerry"
  - West, Julian
  - West, Michael D.
  - Westmoreland, T. David
  - Wexler, Laura J.
  - Wharton, Peter S.
  - Wheatley, James
  - Whedon, Daniel D.
  - Wheeler, Geoffrey
  - Wheeler, Kenneth G.
  - Wheeler, Porter King
  - Whitcomb, Michael
  - White, Cynthia W.
  - White, Duffield
  - White, Elizabeth Alice
  - White, Hayden
  - White, Kathleen
  - White, Marsha Christine
  - White, Stephen D.
  - Whitfield, Kevin
  - Whitlin, Thomson McLintock
  - Whitman, Robert H.
  - Wicks, Sammie Ann
  - Widmer, Ellen
  - Wiggin, Carlton Low
  - Wiggin, Maryann
  - Wilbur, Richard Purdy
  - Williarty, Sarah
  - Willett, William Marinus
  - Williams, Meredith
  - Williamson, Edward
  - Williamson, Kossuth Mayer
  - Willis, Jan
  - Wilson, Barbara-Jan
  - Wilson, Robert D.
  - Wilson, Woodrow
  - Wilson, Whitelaw
  - Winchester, Caleb Thomas
  - Winslow, Kitty Sweet
  - Winston, Krishna Ricarda
  - Winter, David G.
  - Winter, Sarah Kinne
  - Wiseman, Richard J.
  - Withers, John L. II
  - Witkowski, Steve
  - Wolf, John H.
  - Wolfe, Jason S.
  - Wolfe, Robert
  - Wolfzahn, Felice
  - Wons, Maria Mei-ha
  - Wonnacot, Tom
  - Wood, Carol
  - Wood, John Lawrence
  - Wood, Robert C.
  - Woodbridge, Homer Edwards
  - Wu, Konrad T.
  - Wulbert, Roland
  - Wu, Ta-Sun
  - Wu, Wei-Ping
  - Wylie, Dorshka
  - Yanai, Hila
  - Yeager, Robert F.
  - Yohe, Gary W.
  - Yon, Andre
  - Young, Brigitte F.
  - Young, Glenn
  - Young, Michael
  - Young-Bruehl, Elisabeth
  - Yun, Grace
  - Yun, Janet
  - Zabriskie, Franklin R.
  - Zaleski, Philip
  - Zeichner, Abraham M.
  - Zellen, Barry
  - Zhang, Xian-Man
  - Zhou, Haoxuan
  - Zieman, Katherine
  - Zimring, Rishona Elena
  - Zinik, Zinovy
  - Zita, David F.
  - Zlotkowski, Edward A.
  - Zwelling, Jeremy
- Fraternities, Sororities, and Honor Societies
  - Fraternities
    - General I
    - General II
    - General III
    - Fraternity Houses- General
    - Fraternity Houses- Photos (Unidentified interior)
    - Alpha Chi Rho, 1911-1958
    - Alpha Chi Rho, House
    - Alpha Chi Rho, HousePhotos
    - Alpha Chi Rho, Photos (members)
    - Alpha Delta Phi I
    - Alpha Delta Phi II
    - Alpha Delta Phi House
    - Alpha Delta Phi I-Photos
    - Alpha Delta Phi II-Photos
    - Alpha Delta Phi House--photos
    - Alpha Literary Society
    - Beta Theta Pi, 1890-
    - Beta Theta Pi, Photos
    - Beta Theta Pi, House
    - Beta Theta Pi, HousePhoto
    - Beta Theta Pi, Symposium
    - Chi Psi, 1844-1863, 1876-2002
    - Chi Psi Photos
    - Chi Psi House
    - Chi Psi HousePhotos
    - Commons Club (Sigma Chi) I
    - Commons Club (Sigma Chi) II
    - Commons Club (Sigma Chi) III
    - Commons Club (Sigma Chi) Photos
    - Commons Club (Sigma Chi) House
    - Commons Club (Sigma Chi) HousePhotos
    - Delta Tau Delta 1891-1902, 1902-
    - Delta Tau Delta Photos
    - Delta Tau Delta House
    - Delta Tau Delta HousePhotos
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon I (1867- )
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon IPhotos
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon II
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon IIPhotos
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon III
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon House
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon HousePhotos I
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon HousePhotos II
    - Delta Upsilon (est 1850)
    - Esse Quam Videri, 1958-1968
    - Esse Quam Videri, Photos
    - Gamma Psi 1919-28; 1952-
    - Gamma Psi Photos
    - Gamma Psi House
    - Gamma Psi HousePhotos
    - Ivy Club 1928-1933 Photos
    - John Wesley Club 1936-1965
    - John Wesley Club Photos
    - Kappa Alpha 1967-70; 1975
    - Kappa Alpha Photos
    - Kappa Alpha House
    - Kappa Alpha HousePhotos
    - Kappa Alpha Psi
    - Kappa Nu Kappa (Formally Sigma Nu) 1959-
    - Kappa Nu Kappa (Formally Sigma Nu) Photos
    - Kappa Nu Kappa (Formally Sigma Nu) HousePhotos
    - Kappa Rho Sigma (1907- 1909)
    - Lambda Psi Delta
    - Lamda Upsilon Lamda
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- I
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- II
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- III
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- House
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- Photos I
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- Photos II
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- Photos III
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- House Photos I
    - Psi Nu Theta (Eclectic) 1837- House Photos II
    - Psi Upsilon 1843- I
    - Psi Upsilon 1843- II
    - Psi Upsilon 1843- House
    - Psi Upsilon 1843- Photos I
    - Psi Upsilon 1843- Photos II
    - Psi Upsilon 1843- House Photos I
    - Psi Upsilon 1843- House Photos II
    - Theta Delta Chi 1857-1861
  - Sororities
    - Alpha Gamma Delta
    - Delta Delta Delta
    - Delta Sigma Theta
    - Kappa Alpha Theta
    - Lambda Pi Chi/ Latinas Promoviendo Comunidad
    - Phi Sigma-- Photos
    - Zeta Phi Beta
  - Honor Societies
    - Cardinal Key
    - Cardinal Key Photos
    - Corpse and Coffin, 1872-1924
    - Corpse and Coffin Photos
    - Kappa Gamma (Kai Gar) 1872-1910
    - Kappa Gamma (Kai Gar) Photos
    - Lambda Rho Society 1877-1888 (Freshmen secret society)
    - Mystic Seven 1873-
    - Mystic Seven Photos
    - Mystic Seven Alumni Assn., Inc.
    - Omicron Delta Epsilon (Economics)
    - Phi Beta Kappa
    - Phi Beta Kappa Photos
    - Phi Kappa Tau 1891-1910
    - Phi Kappa Tau Photos
    - Sigma Tau 1896-1922
    - Sigma XI 1935-
    - Skull and Serpent
    - Skull and Serpent Photos
    - Theta Nu Epsilon 1870-1910, 1931-
    - Theta Nu Epsilon Photos
    - Zeta Phi 1877-1910
    - Zeta Phi Photos
- Graduate Programs
  - Graduate Liberal Studies Program, 1979-2000
  - Graduate Liberal Studies Program, 2000-
  - Graduate Summer School for Teachers, 1953-1979
  - Master of Arts in Teaching
  - Graduate study, sciences (see also: MA and MS Committee on Graduate Instruction, specific departments)
  - Music: PhD program in ethnomusicology
- Honors
  - Latin
  - Honors, 1888-
  - Honors College, 1968-
  - Honors College: Reports, 1962-1988
  - Honors College programs, 1966-
  - Honors College: Photos
- Middletown
  - African/African Americans in Middletown
  - Anniversary Celebrations
  - Archaeology
  - ArtFarm
  - Artists, Engravers
  - AWARE (the Association of Wesleyan Area Residents)
  - Beman Family
  - Biographyaccounts, diaries, memorials
  - Biography (reminiscences)
  - Business and Industry
  - Cemeteries and Churches
  - Censuses
  - Churches
  - Citizens Advisory Council (CAC)
  - Clean Sweep
  - Community Health Center
  - Connecticut Juvenile Training School
  - Connecticut Valley Hospital
  - Cross Street A.M.E. Zion Church
  - Disasters: Fires
  - Disasters: Storms
  - Governmental/Administration
  - Greater Middletown Preservation Trust
  - History, General
  - Houses, Buildings, Streets
  - Houses, Buildings, Streets: Wetmore House
  - Iconography
  - Immigrants, ethnic groups
  - Imprints
  - Indians
  - Inn at Middletown
  - Kiwanis, The
  - Leatherman
  - Libraries & Bookstores
  - Libraries & BookstoresMiddletownRussell Library
  - Middletown Lodging
  - Middletown (Newspaper)
  - Maps
  - Medicine and Health
  - Middlesex Community College
  - Middlesex County Historical Society
  - Middlesex Lantern
  - Middletown Commission on the Arts
  - Monuments
  - Music
  - Nearby Towns
  - Newspapers
  - North End
  - North End Action Team (NEAT)
  - Oddfellows Playhouse Theater
  - ORourkes
  - Quarries
  - Railroads & Other Transportation
  - Restaurants and Food Stores (see also O'Rourke's)
  - Schools, Students K-12
  - Sports
  - Stearns Family
  - Temperance
  - Trees and Parks
  - Wadsworth Mansion
  - Wadsworth State Park
  - Waterfront, Bridge, River and Shipping
  - Wesleyan Hills
  - Wesleyan-Middletown Relations, 1917-1979
  - Wesleyan-Middletown Relations, 1980-1995
  - Wesleyan-Middletown Relations, 1996-
  - Wetlands
  - Middletown Photographs
    - Berkeley Divinity School
    - Churches
    - Disasters: Fires
    - Disasters: Floods
    - Disasters: Storms
    - Individuals
    - Miscellaneous
    - Panoramas of Middletown
    - Quarries
    - Railroads and other transportation
    - Schools
    - Streets: General
    - Streets: High Street
    - Streets: Main Street
    - Waterfront
    - Waterfront: Portland Bridges
- Paintings and Objects
  - Chair, Hitchcock
  - (Governor) Winthrop Chair
  - Coins and Medals
  - The Gym Key
  - Melville Collection (Pottery)
  - Bricher Landscape
  - Dyer
  - Paintings and Drawings
  - Portrait Paintings
  - Portrait PaintingsRestoration
  - Pewter Collection
  - Scientific Apparatus and Technicians
  - Astronomical Instruments Queries
  - Scientific Apparatus: Orrery (Columbian) 1837
  - Scientific Apparatus: Astronomical Instruments, Various
  - Scientific Apparatus: 6" Telescope
  - Scientific Apparatus: 12" Telescope
  - Scientific Apparatus: 18.5" Telescope
  - Scientific Apparatus: 20" Telescope, Van Vleck Observatory
  - Scientific Apparatus: 24" Telescope
  - Scientific Apparatus: Calorimeter
  - Stationary
  - Elizabethan Table
  - World Instrument Collection
- Presidents
  - Presidents, General
  - Presidents, General, Searches
  - Bangs, Nathan
  - Bangs, Nathanportraits
  - Beach, John Wesley, class of 1845
  - Beach, John Wesleyportraits
  - Bennet, Douglas J., class of 1959
  - Bennet, Douglas J.Inauguration
  - Bennet, Douglas J.Presidential Search, 1994
  - Bennet, Douglas J.Writings/Speeches
  - Butterfield, Victor L. (2)
  - Butterfield, Victor L.Inaugural
  - Butterfield, Victor L.Photos
  - Butterfield, Victor L.Writings
  - Campbell, Colin Goetze (2)
  - Campbell, Colin GoetzeInaugural
  - Campbell, Colin GoetzeWritings
  - Chace, William Murdough
  - Chace, William MurdoughInaugural
  - Chace, William MurdoughSearch, selection, pre-inaugural
  - Chace, William MurdoughWritings
  - Cummings, Joseph
  - Cummings, JosephPhotos
  - Etherington, Edwin
  - Etherington, EdwinWritings
  - Fisk, Willbur
  - Fisk, WillburGravesite
  - Fisk, WillburPortraits
  - Fisk, WillburWritings
  - Foss, Cyrus David
  - Foss, Cyrus DavidInaugural
  - Foss, Cyrus DavidPortraits
  - Foss, Cyrus DavidWritings
  - McConaughy, James Lukens
  - McConaughy, James LukensInaugural
  - McConaughy, James LukensPortraits
  - McConaughy, James LukensWritings
  - Olin, Stephen
  - Olin, StephenPortraits
  - Olin, StephenWritings
  - Raymond, Bradford Paul
  - Raymond, Bradford PaulInaugural
  - Raymond, Bradford PaulPortraits
  - Raymond, Bradford PaulWritings
  - Roth, Michael
  - Shanklin, William Arnold
  - Shanklin, William ArnoldInauguration (2)
  - Shanklin, William ArnoldInauguration photos
  - Shanklin, William ArnoldPortraits
  - Smith, Augustus W.
  - Smith, Augustus W.Portraits
  - Smith, Augustus W.Writings
- Related Individuals and Organizations
  - Adams, John
  - Albright, Madeline
  - Aldington, Richard
  - Alsop Family
  - American Association of University Women
  - American Building Management
  - American Literary, Scientific, and Military Academy
  - American Literary, Scientific, and Military AcademyExhibit
  - Anderson, Sherwood
  - Angelou, Maya
  - Armstrong, Louis
  - Astronomical Society of Greater Hartford
  - Atticus
  - Auden, W. H.
  - Bacon, Henry
  - Baldwin, James
  - Barnes, (Edward) Duane
  - Barrett, Joseph, M.D.
  - Brant, Henry
  - Brown, Elmer Ellsworth
  - Buttonwood Tree
  - Cage, John
  - Camps Palestine Garden
  - Carberry, Josiah S.
  - Cardinal Printers
  - Carter, Stephen L.
  - Cazenovia Seminary
  - Center for Creative Youth
  - Chess: Connecticut Closed
  - Choice
  - Colton, Walter
  - Le Corbusier
  - Crane, Stephen
  - Daly, Mary
  - Davis, Angela
  - Denzing, Richard Lawrence
  - Dickens, Charles (High Street)
  - Dodd, Christopher
  - Duncan, Robert
  - Eastwood, Clint
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David
  - Eliot, T. S.
  - Ellison, Ralph
  - Emerson, Ralph Waldo
  - Emory & Henry College
  - Essex Marine Laboratory
  - Farrakhan, Louis
  - Fo, Dano
  - Franklin, William
  - Free University
  - Frost, Robert
  - Fuller, Buckminster
  - Gilead House
  - Gilder, Richard W.
  - Ginsberg, Allan
  - Goodspeed Opera House
  - Gore, Al
  - Grateful Dead
  - Great Hollow Wilderness SchoolWesleyan Orientation in the Wilderness
  - Green Street Arts Center
  - Habitat for Humanity
  - Hayes, Rutherford B.
  - Herring, Henry
  - Hill Corporation
  - Hill, Rodney
  - Hoffman, Abbie
  - How to Change a Flat Tire
  - Hubbard Family
  - Hugo, Harold
  - Institute for the Future
  - Jackson, Andrew
  - Jefferson, Thomas
  - Juba
  - Kazan, Elia
  - Kids on Campus
  - King, Martin Luther
  - Kapit, Arthur
  - Lafayette
  - Langer, Suzanne
  - Lawrence University
  - Lemon, Ralph
  - Lee, Jason
  - Liddy, G. Gordon
  - Little Three
  - Lockwood, Theodore Davidge
  - Long Lane Farm
  - Long Lane School
  - Lummis, William De Fletcher
  - Magill, Captain Charles
  - Mailer, Norman
  - Malcolm X
  - Mann, Thomas
  - March of Dimes
  - Maritain, Jacques
  - Math Clinic
  - McKenzie, R. Tait
  - Meridians
  - Moodus Noises
  - Mt. Allison University
  - Moynihan, Daniel P.
  - Naipaul, V. S.
  - Nature Conservency (Connecticut Chapter)
  - Neighborhood Preschool
  - Nixon, Richard
  - Oddfellows Playhouse
  - Olmert, Dr. Yossi
  - Oko, Yono
  - Ordwes
  - Oz, Amos
  - Peterson, Roger Tory
  - Pinsky, Robert
  - Postal Service, U. S.
  - Presley, Elvis
  - Press Archives
  - Quindlen, Anna
  - Red Cross
  - Roach, Max
  - Rockfall, Corporation
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President
  - Root, Elihu
  - Russell, Samuel
  - Russell Family Papers
  - Said, Edward
  - Sandberg, Carl
  - Schorr, Daniel
  - Seeger, Pete
  - Shaw, Gwendolyn Du Bois
  - Singer, Peter
  - Smith, Harriet A. Walker
  - Snow, C. P.
  - Sonomama Improvisational Dance-Theater
  - Sprinkle, Annie
  - Stein, Gertrude
  - Strand, Mark
  - Students Wives Organization
  - Summer programs and camps
  - Sun-Up Press
  - Supreme Court, Connecticut
  - Surdna Foundation
  - Taft, William Howard
  - Talking Drums
  - Teach for America
  - Teen Life Conference
  - Thomas, Norman
  - Trinity College Chapel: Wesleyan pew
  - Tudor, David
  - Tutu, Desmond
  - United Nations Association of the United States
  - United Way
  - Upward Bound
  - Van Vleck, John
  - Wadsworth, Clarence Seymour
  - Warren, Robert Penn
  - Washington, George
  - Waters, John
  - Webb, Isaac School
  - Wesley, JohnGeneral
  - Wesley, JohnIconography
  - Wesley, Johnat Wesleyan University
  - Wesleyan Potters
  - West China Union University
  - Westmoreland, Gen. William
  - Whitefield, George
  - Wilbraham Academy
  - Wilson, Edmund
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd
  - Writers Conference
  - Young, Andrew
  - Zygo Corporation
- Scholarships and Prizes
  - Fellowships
  - Prizes- Miscellaneous
  - John Blanchard Clark Fellowship, 1967
  - Etherington scholarships
  - Prizes and Prizes Awards (2)
  - Freeman Asian Scholars Program
  - Agnes G. Gilman, class of 1897 Scholarship
  - Guggenheim Fellowship
  - Hallowell Prize
  - Jackson Cup, 1913-1959
  - Maynard Memorial Award
  - McConaughy Award
  - Mellon Minority Undergraduate Fellowship Program
  - Rhodes Scholars 1904-
  - Rich Prize
  - Watson
  - Scholarships and Loans
  - Student Leadership Recognition Program
  - Student Leadership Recognition Award
  - Winchester, Caleb T., Teacher Award
- Student Clubs and Activities
  - General Information
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), Wesleyan
  - Aeronautics
  - African Students Association
  - Ajua Campos
  - Anti-Oppression House
  - Sexual Health Awareness (ASHA)/ Student Global AIDS Campaign
  - Asian American Cooperative Theatre
  - Asian/ Pacific American Alliance (APAA)
  - Atwater Club
  - Bands and Orchestras
  - Bands and OrchestrasPhotos
  - Bayit
  - Bell and Scroll Guild
  - Black and Latino Brotherhood
  - The Browning Society
  - Buddhist House
  - Camera Club
  - Canoe Club
  - Canon
  - Capoeira Club
  - Captain Partridge Studio Theatre
  - Cardinal Sinners
  - CardinalsPhotos
  - Chique Chaque Club
  - Christian Association YMCA I
  - Christian Association YMCA II
  - Christian Association YMCA Photos
  - Christian Association YMCA Italian Mission
  - Christian Fellowship
  - Classical Club
  - Classical ClubPhotos
  - Collegio ad Absurdum
  - Community Service
  - Copus (Coalition of Independent, College, and University Students)
  - Creative Christian Collective
  - Cunt Club
  - Cuvierian Society
  - Daffodil Days
  - Debate 1855-1910
  - Debate 1911-
  - Debate Photos
  - Deutsche Verein I Photos
  - Deutsche Verein II Photos
  - Ebony Singers
  - E3
  - Environmental Organizers Network (EON)
  - 8 to 8
  - English as a Second Language
  - Focus on Eating Disorder Understanding Prevention (FEDUP)
  - Film; Film Making
  - Fly Fishing Club
  - Food Not Bombs
  - Food Recovery Coalition (FoRC)
  - French Club Photos
  - Ultimate Frisbee
  - Gag Reflex
  - Gay, Bisexuals, Lesbians of Color and Questioning (GBLOCQ)
  - Glee and Mandolin Club
  - Glee Club
  - Group for Independent Analysis
  - Habitat for Humanity
  - Heathen House
  - Havurah
  - Hellenic Club
  - The Highwaymen
  - Holocaust Remembrance Day
  - Hunt Club/ Saturday Groupe
  - Integrity and Mobility for the Poor through Access to Capital Today (IMPACT!)
  - Intercultural House
  - International Relations Club
  - Interracial Students Organization
  - Jibers General
  - Jibers Photos
  - Live Wolves! Co-op
  - LYPsinners
  - Lysistrata Project
  - Medieval House
  - Mock Trial
  - Model United Nations
  - Musical Groups General
  - Musical Groups Choral
  - Musical Plays
  - Muslim Student Organization
  - New World Consort
  - Onomatopoeia
  - Oratorical Contests 1847-1900
  - Oratorical Contests 1901-
  - Outing Club General
  - Outing Club Photos
  - PADThai
  - Paint and Powder Club, Miscellaneous Dramatic Groups General
  - Paint and Powder Club, Miscellaneous Dramatic Groups IPhotos
  - Paint and Powder Club, Miscellaneous Dramatic Groups IIPhotos
  - Paint and Powder Club, Miscellaneous Dramatic Groups III- Photos
  - Pangea
  - Physiological Society
  - Ping- Pong Club
  - Poets (Students)
  - Praying Band
  - Pre-Medical ClubPhotos
  - Presidential Address Organization
  - The Progressive Club
  - Prometheus
  - Punchline
  - Queer Alliance
  - Refuse and Resist
  - Rosa ClubPhotos
  - Science ClubsPhotos
  - Scrabble Club (WeScrabble)
  - Scrawlers
  - Second Stage
  - Sexual Education Counseling Service (SECS)
  - Shakti
  - Sign Language House
  - Smoking Club
  - Social Committee
  - Social Study Club
  - Spanish Club
  - Student Alliance to Reform Corporations (STARC)
  - Student Art Gallery
  - Student of Color Council
  - Student Forums
  - Student Global Aids Campaign (SGAC)
  - Student League for Industrial Democracy
  - Students for Access to Health Care (SAHC)
  - Students for Clean Elections
  - Students for Ending the War in Iraq (SEWI)
  - Students for a Free Palestine
  - Students for a Free Tibet (SFT)
  - Students for Israel
  - Students for Peace in Iraq Now (SPIN)
  - Students Organized Against Racism
  - Students for Sensible Drug Policy (SSDP)
  - Student Unity Network
  - Sustainable Building Club
  - Terpsichore
  - Time Is Management, Management Is Time (TIMMIT)
  - Ujamaa
  - Urban Renewal (Musical Group)
  - United Student/ Labor Action Coalition (USLAC)
  - Volunteer Fire Department
  - Well-Being House
  - Wesleyan Asian/ Asian American Student Union (WA/AASU)
  - Wesleyan Asian Students Party (WASP)
  - Wesleyan Association of Word Awareness (WAWA)
  - Wesleyan Cannabis Coalition
  - Wesleyan Cinema Club, 1936-1943
  - Wesleyan Democrats
  - Wesleyan Film Board/ Film Series
  - Wesleyan Investment Group
  - Wesleyan Linguistic Society/ WesLS
  - Wesleyan Mountaineering Club (WMC)
  - Wesleyan Opposition and Liberation Front (WOLF)
  - Wesleyan Organized Medical Action Network (WOMAN)
  - Wesleyan Peer Mediation Program (WPMP)